Contact

Egypt 01015185283 (Mobile) mohamedabdelradyahmed00@gma il.com

www.linkedin.com/in/mohamedabdelrady (LinkedIn) aburehab.com (Personal)

Top Skills

WordPress
Wix Website Builder
Webflow

Mohamed Abd-Elrady

Frontend Developer

Egypt

Summary

I am a front-end developer with three years of experience in building responsive websites.

I use HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS, JavaScript, jQuery,

ECMAScript, TypeScript, React, Next.js, and Node.

To build big web projects, I use template engines and preprocessors PugJs, Sass, and using Task Runner GulpJs.

I know testing with Jest and experience with clean, performanceoptimized designs.

Experience

Upwork

Frontend Developer

2019 - Present (5 years)

Building web applications using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript,

ECMAScript, jQuery.

Building big web projects using template engine and preprocessors PugJs,

Sass and using Task Runner GulpJs

Freelancer.com

Frontend Developer

2016 - Present (8 years)

Building web applications using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript,

ECMAScript, jQuery.

Building big web projects using template engine and preprocessors PugJs,

Sass and using Task Runner GulpJs

Education

El Shorouk Academy

Bachelor's degree, Computer and Information Sciences · (2014 - 2018)